benefitsandwork.co.uk 2018-12-28

# Privacy & Cookies

### We are:

Benefits and Work Publishing Ltd.   
Registered office: 8-10 Queen Street, Seaton, Devon EX12 2NY  
Country of registration: United Kingdom **  
** Company Registration No. 05962666  
VAT Registration Number: 931571333

**Mailing address**  
Benefits and Work Publishing Ltd  
PO Box 63  
AXMINSTER  
EX13 9AP

### **Visitors to the site**

This website uses session cookies which are deleted when you close your browser. They allow you to move from page to page of the site without having to continually log in again, for example.

This site also uses persistent cookies if you tick the 'Remember me' box when you log in, so that you can revisit the site without having to log in every time.

We also use Google Analytics to collect anonymous data about such things as how many people visit the site, what pages they land on and how long they stay on each page. If you do not want your visits to websites to be tracked by Google Analytics [you can opt out here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

You can find out more about cookies, how to remove them and how to prevent them being placed on your computer at [All About Cookies](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/)

We also log visitors internet protocol (IP) addresses for system administration purposes.

### **Website subscribers**

If you subscribe to the site as a claimant or carer you provide us with: an email address; your choice of username, which is not shown to other users; your choice of display (forum) name, which is visible to other users if you post in the forum or post a comment; your choice of password, which is encrypted and we do not have access to.

You can change your email address, password and forum name on the site.

To do so, first log into the site, then either follow this link:

<http://www.benefitsandwork.co.uk/component/users/profile>

or click on the 'Register' link at the top right of the page.

You will be taken to your Profile page.

Click on the Edit profile button.

Make any changes you wish to make and then click on the Submit button.

Professional users who pay by invoice also provide us with a physical address and the name of the person to whom invoices should be addressed.

Payment is made using payment processors PayPal or Worldpay who will collect data form you according to the requirements of their systems. At no time do we have access to your financial details, these are all dealt with by the payment processors.

You can [read Paypal’s privacy policy here](https://www.icontact.com/legal/privacy).

You can [read Worldpay’s privacy policy here](https://www.worldpay.com/uk/privacy-policy).

Website subscribers also have access to our forum. No additional details need to be provided to use the forum and we do not provide any facility by which forum users can private message each other.

We will email you at the start of your subscription to inform you that it has begun and we will email you shortly before your subscription ends to offer you the opportunity to resubscribe at a reduced rate for renewals. Apart from this we will not send you any emails unless there is a specific reason to do so in connection with the management of the site, such as a problem with your access.

### **Newsletter subscribers**

If you sign up to our fortnightly newsletter you will need to provide an email address and your choice of name you wish to be addressed by.

This is separate from the details you provide to subscribe to the website. These details are processed by our mailing list management provider, icontact, a company based in the United States. You can [read icontact’s privacy policy here](https://www.icontact.com/legal/privacy).

We collect statistics relating to email opens and clicks to help us monitor and improve the readability of our newsletters.

At the bottom of every newsletter there is a ‘Manage my subscription link’ which allows you to change your details or opt out of receiving any more emails from us.

### **Access to your personal information**

If you have any queries about the way we process your data or if you want to know what data we hold on you, please email us at [admin@benefitsandwork.co.uk](mailto:admin@benefitsandwork.co.uk)

### **Changes to our privacy notice**

This privacy notice was last updated on 24 May 2018.It will be reviewed regularly and altered as required. Please check back if you wish to see the most up-to-date version. The information here is not exhaustive, so please contact us if there is anything else you wish to know about how we manage your personal information.
